{
    "id": "497741c3866743a7b992d1d052233203",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "After ……………………… this form, give it to the secretary.",
            "description": "After + ing can be used instead of after + subject + verb. This sentence can also be written as:\r\nAfter you have completed this form, give it to the secretary.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "complete",
                "completing",
                "completed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "After the movie we had dinner and went to a night club then we ………………………… went home.",
            "description": "After all does not mean finally.",
            "answers": [
                "lastly",
                "after all",
                "finally"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Give me some soup ……………………",
            "description": "We do not normally use also in imperative sentences.",
            "answers": [
                "as well as",
                "also",
                "as well"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. I don’t like him, I think he is honest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Even if",
                "As though"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The shop is open from Monday ………………… Saturday.",
            "description": "In American English, either through or to can be used here. In British English, to is preferred.",
            "answers": [
                "through",
                "to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She has bought …………………… car.",
            "description": "Another means extra or additional. It is used with singular countable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "another",
                "an other",
                "other"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is unhappy because she has got ………………….. friends.",
            "description": "No means the same as not any, but it is more emphatic.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some",
                "no"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If I were …………………… younger, I would marry you.",
            "description": "Any can modify comparatives. This is common after if.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What time does the sun ……………………?",
            "description": "Rise means get higher or come up.",
            "answers": [
                "rise",
                "arise",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… must have patience.",
            "description": "A singular countable noun must have an article with it. A teacher means any teacher.",
            "answers": [
                "Teacher",
                "A teacher",
                "The teacher"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. usually start walking at around one year old.",
            "description": "We do not use articles with plural and uncountable nouns to talk about people or things in general.",
            "answers": [
                "Children",
                "The children",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a cat ……………………. the bed.",
            "description": "Under and underneath can both indicate physical position.",
            "answers": [
                "under",
                "underneath",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}